

Riccardo.Gelosa@outlook.it

+39 338 754 0333

Github.com/JasonLeack

Linkedin.com/in/riccardo-gelosa

PROGRAMMING

C Based Java

SQL Python

Javascript | HTML/CSS

HLSL/GLSL Visual Basic

TOOLS

Unreal Igr

Ignition

Blender

Docker

NOWN LANGUAGES

ItalianMother tongue

EnglishFull professional proficiency



Riccardo Gelosa

Software developer

Carate Brianza (MB), Italy - 20841

20/06/1997

I'm a software developer with experience in the industrial automation field on all steps of the project, starting from creating simulations of the machine in the plant to the commissioning on the field, accompanied by supervision systems and MES integration.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCES

Software developer

CAPP, Milan (MI), Italy 07/2022 – TODAY

- Development of tools and simulations of industrial plants to verify the performance and feasibility using game engines
- Development of supervision systems to gather data from the field and create interfaces using SCADA platforms
- Creation and administration of SQL databases
- Drafting of technical specifications for our machines
- □ Field trips to commission machines and on site assistance
- Interfacing between clients and suppliers, technical consulting
- Creation of web apps using Angular framework

Production & TPM/Continuous Improvement

Owens Corning, Besana Brianza (MB), Italy 08/2021 - 07/2022

- **TPM e Continuous Improvement** coach assistant
- Creation of standard operative procedure and operator training
- Development of tools to automate office work, statistical analysis of performances, data logging and management of internal archives
- -Autonomous maintenance

EDUCATION

Diploma in information technology

ITIS P. Hensemberger, Monza (MB) 09/2014 – 06/2017

PERSONAL INTERESTS AND HOBBIES

- Game development
- 2D drawing and 3D modeling
- Historical fencing
- Miniatures

Take a look at my portfolio: https://jasonleack.github.io/